buyhitscheap.com 2006-06-27

# BuyHitsCheap.com : Real Website Visitors, Guaranteed.

** Website Traffic**

Send up to one million real people directly to your website or online advertisement in one month. Watch your stats grow in real-time with our Client Control Panel!

**Learn More** **     Order Now** ** Regional Traffic**

Need to market your website to a specific audience? We will deliver quality web traffic based on the country of web visitor that you choose. Choose from 4 Regional categories.

**Learn More** **     Order Now** **Questions & Answers**

Q. What is a "Unique Visitor"? 

A. Unique visits are counted when someone views a web page for the first time. 

**Read More** ****

| 

During registration, BuyHitsCheap.com will gather personal information such as your name and email address, your street address, billing information, and the URL of your web site. This information is used solely by BuyHitsCheap.com to provide services to you or to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it. Once you register you are no longer anonymous - you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of BuyHitsCheap.com. 

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place listings or take advantage of the other features of BuyHitsCheap.com. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Every page within BuyHitsCheap.com includes a link to this Privacy Policy.

As a general rule, we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below.

BuyHitsCheap.com may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of the website, other users of the website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. BuyHitsCheap.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may edit or delete your user profile at any time by clicking on the "My Profile" link or graphic provided by the system once you are logged in. Once you have logged onto the system during a given session, wherever you go on BuyHitsCheap.com, your information will stay with you until or unless you click on the "Logoff" link, which is accessible from within the "My Profile" screen. 

If you are a previously registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may obtain it by email by using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the button on any login page to request that your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means. 

Your BuyHitsCheap.com account can be deleted, but doing so will result in not being able to access any of the features of the program that require user registration.

Other than the administrator of the BuyHitsCheap.com or other authorized personnel of the website, you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access. 

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session in the system. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

|
